联系方式

www.linkedin.com/in/mingj2 (LinkedIn) mingjin.dev (Portfolio)

热门技能

Graph Neural Networks
Deep Learning
Time Series Analysis

Languages

English (Full Professional)
Chinese (Native or Bilingual)

Publications

ANEMONE: Graph Anomaly Detection with Multi-Scale Contrastive Learning

Neural Temporal Walks: Motif-Aware Representation Learning on Continuous-Time Dynamic Graphs

Multivariate Time Series Forecasting with Dynamic Graph Neural ODEs

Multi-Scale Contrastive Siamese Networks for Self-Supervised Graph Representation Learning

Graph Self-Supervised Learning: A Survey

Ming Jin

Ph.D. Researcher at Monash University

澳洲 Victoria 墨尔本

个人简介

I am a Ph.D. researcher at Monash University under the supervision of Prof. Shirui Pan and A/Prof. Yuan-Fang Li since Fall 2020. Before this, I have achieved my Master's degree from the University of Melbourne in 2019 and worked as an Al/ML engineer at Metso Outotec since Fall 2018.

工作经历

Monash University Research Assistant 2020 年 8 月 - Present (3 年 3 个月)

Clayton, Victoria, Australia

Metso Outotec

Al Research & Development Engineer 2020年1月-2020年6月(6个月) Melbourne, Victoria, Australia

Outotec

1年3个月

Al Research & Development Intern 2019 年 3 月 - 2020 年 1 月 (11 个月)

Melbourne, Australia

Summer Intern - ML/AI Research 2018年11月-2019年2月(4个月)

Melbourne, Australia

教育经历

Monash University

Doctor of Philosophy - PhD, Machine Learning · (2020 - 2024)

University of Melbourne

Master's degree, Information Technology · (2018 - 2020)

Hebei University of Technology

Bachelor's degree, Intelligent Science and Technology · (2013 - 2017)